(upbeat rock music)
♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ We're down in Deep 13. ♪
♪ Dr. Forester and TV's Frank ♪
♪ Were hatching an evil scheme ♪
♪ They hired a temp
by the name of Mike ♪
♪ Just a regular Joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ Their experiment
needed a good test case ♪
♪ So they conked
him on the noggin ♪
♪ And they shot him into space ♪
- [Mike] Get me out!
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can
find, la la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor
his mind, la la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
I can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end, la la la ♪
♪ He can try to
keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot role call ♪
- [Scientists] Cambot!
- Kill yourself.
- [Scientists] Gypsy!
Tom Servo.
- Hello there.
- [Scientists] Crow!
♪ If you wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science
facts, la la la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(equipment whirring)
- Oh, I don't know.
Hi, everyone, welcome
to Satellite Love,
we're just kinda sitting
around waiting for Tom Servo.
- Waiting for Tom.
- Man, where the heck
is that guy anyway,
and what's he up to?
- I don't know.
- What's he up to?
- Said he had
something to show us.
- Something to show us.
- Oh I can hardly wait.
- Ta da!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Hey, pretty
impressive, eh folks?
I tell ya I feel like a new man.
- I feel ill.
- I know what you're thinking.
Kerry Grant, right,
I can see that sure.
Maybe a little touch
of Seinfeld (laughs).
You know I'm weighing several
new career options fellas.
Politics, TV, news, ha,
I'm even considering
franchising the look!
Maybe a series of infommericals!
Hey kids, you gotta get
ahead, get a head (laughs).
- Get him!
- Don't mess up the hair!
- I'll mess it up.
(funky techno music)
- I know what it is, Mike,
you're threatened
by my good looks.
Is that it, is that it?
- Yeah.
Yeah that's it buddy.
(robots screaming)
Hey, hey, hey look,
the things are sorry.
(gentle horn music)
♪ I was alone with
the world to tame ♪
♪ I was evil but feeling blue ♪
♪ Lookin' around,
talkin' to clowns ♪
♪ Never guessin'
that I'd find you ♪
♪ Working the fryer
I was never a crier ♪
♪ I had a void in
the shape of you ♪
♪ Lookin' for love,
hopin' for evil ♪
♪ All's I got was
chicken cordon bleu ♪
♪ But a bean ♪
♪ We're living in Deep 13 ♪
♪ Nobody knows what we mean ♪
♪ Ruling the world with
our heads in a swirl ♪
♪ And it's keen ♪
♪ Living in Deep 13. ♪
Thank you, thank you.
- Thank you Frankie.
Folks at home, Mike,
little friends,
you're gonna be seeing a
lot of changes around here.
- We're softening to
reach a wider audience.
- That's right and as
the world is enchanted
with our whimsy we'll slowly
take over their minds.
- What a hoot (laughs).
But first we need you guys
to help out by writing
your own theme songs.
- You know to
increase your share.
So go ahead, give it a try.
- Oh, goodie, goodie, goodie,
goodie, goodie, goodie,
oh can I go first?
- Oh boy here we go.
- Please guys can I go
first, please, please.
I've had my theme song
ready since infancy
now finally someone has the
good sense to request it.
- Okay, if you're that eager
to help Dr. Forester hey,
I can't stop you.
(tense opera music)
♪ Tom ♪
♪ Servo ♪
♪ Glorious Tom Servo ♪
- (whistles) Understated.
♪ Wonderful Tom ♪
♪ Magnific Tom Tom Servo ♪
♪ Bigger than life ♪
♪ Bigger than you ♪
♪ You wanna ♪
- Okay, get him off,
I think that started
to cut his lights back.
- Of course there is.
- Oh there is?
- Yeah.
- Oh I'm sorry, I
thought that was the end,
sorry about that.
But as long as we're stopped,
Crow, dive in, theme song.
- Uh, uh, la, la,
la, la, la, la, Crow.
La, la, la, la, la,
la, la, uh, Crow.
La, la, la, la,
la, la, la, Crow.
- That's it?
- Yeah.
- That's good.
- Oh, thank you.
- I liked it, especially
that one part.
- Okay, Nelson, let's hear it.
- Oh I don't have
one, you know me.
- Typical, typical.
- Well I'll save
your bacon Mike.
Mike, ma, ma, ma, Mike, ma,
ma, ma, Mike, Mike, Mike,
Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike,
Mike, ma, ma, ma, Mike,
ma, ma, ma, Mike, Mike,
Mike, Mike, Mike, ma, ma, ma,
Mike, Mike, Mike, ma, ma,
ma, Mike, ma, Mike, ma, ma!
Mike.
- Okay great thank you
for saving my bacon.
- No problem.
And there it is,
there's the theme songs,
hope you like 'em.
- Yes.
- Mike, Mike, Mike, ma, ma,
ma, Mike, ma, ma, ma, Mike--
- Those were good,
maybe a bit too good.
At least we're all
on the same page.
- Ma, ma, ma, Mike, Mike, Mike.
- Anyway Nelson--
- I love Kramer.
- Well you know, oh, your
movie this week is, well bad.
- Ma, ma, ma, Mike.
- It was written by Ed Wood
so get out your favorite
pair of poms and have a ball.
But first, there's a
little short by my friends
at Jam Handy!
Frank!
- Ma, ma, ma, Mike!
- Ed Wood, no!
(horns blaring)
I have agoraphobia!
(equipment whirring)
(bright music)
- [Tom] Young Man's Fancy
crinkle cut potatoes.
- [Mike] That little character
was in Cats, wasn't he?
- [Crow] Oh you know she's got
a darling triangular figure.
- [Mike] Wow, this
is too titillating.
Are we allowed to watch this?
- [Tom] Oh, she's listening
to her dehumidifier.
- [Mike] I guess teens dig
lush orchestral arrangements.
- [Broadcaster] 12 o'clock
and time for the headlines
of the latest news of the day.
According to the
latest bulletin--
- [Crow] Ironing can be deadly.
- How the sandwiches
coming Momma?
- Almost ready.
They're so easy to do
even your dad can put them
together and do a dandy
burling job on them.
- Dad kinda fancies himself
quite a cook since we
got an electric
range doesn't he?
- Mhmm and he's
pretty good at it too.
Let's have cocoa today.
It'll just take a few
seconds to heat up some milk.
- Okay, I'll be
finished in half a sec.
Mother--
- [Tom] Is space curved?
- Wouldn't it be slick if
we had an electric ironer,
like Sally's mother has.
- Of course it would
and I'm looking forward
to having an electric drier too.
- [Mike] Is she blind?
- Just think, then we'd have
a complete electric laundry.
- Wee!
- [Mom] Wee?
What?
- Goodbye old wash
day that's what, wee!
- [Mom] Really silly.
C'mon now eat your lunch,
you'll feel better.
- I feel fine.
- [Crow] I think they're
both trying way to hard.
- [Mike] Yeah.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- [Mike] Another
lonely Thanksgiving.
- [Crow] Now a cling free.
- Mmm, this tastes yummy.
- [Tom] And all the fats
are numbing my emotions.
- I just love bacon crisp
and crunchy like this.
- [Mike] Yeah, evidently.
- Honey, stop wolfing your food.
No one's gonna take
it away from you.
- Sorry sweetie but
it's really your fault.
Shouldn't make 'em so good.
- [Crow] Whatever happened
to my pet Vietnamese
pot belly pig?
Mom, what's sex?
- Oh I almost forgot,
a letter from Bob.
- [Judy] Another letter?
I thought he was
coming home tomorrow.
- He is.
He wrote to say he's
bringing a friend with him.
- What does he say?
'Bout the friend I mean.
Is he tall dark and
handsome, I hope?
- [Tom] Tee hee, I'm horny.
- Well here's what he says.
Alex is a real great guy,
even though he's
serious minded and tops
in all his classes.
- [Mike] He is my soulmate.
- He's got a job lined up with
a construction gang near us
and I knew you wouldn't mind
if he'd spend a few days with
me since it's the
end of the term.
- Say!
Pretty dull.
- Alex has little
time for girls.
- [Crow] Uh oh!
- I knew it.
I bet he doesn't even dance.
- And is quite a woman
hater in his way.
Well, well.
- For Pete's sake, wouldn't
you know that goon brother
of mine would bring
home something that
lives under a rock?
- Judy, I do wish you'd
speak English like
normal human beings.
Besides, I'm sure Mr. Phipps
is a very nice young man.
- I know, but just because
Bob is a book gook,
it's no reason he has to bring
another one home with him.
- Well we'll see.
Oh there's a special
message for you.
- [Tom] Uh, I loathe you.
- And be sure and tell Judy
to keep her grimy little paws
off of my friend.
He's got no time for babies.
- [Mike] He's not
Jerry Seinfeld.
- What's his name again?
- [Crow] George Kaplan.
- Alexander Phipps.
- Alexander Phipps?
Sounds revolting.
- [Tom] Sounds
Montclair momenty.
- Whatever my dear brother
think I'd be interested
in a character with
a name like that?
- [Tom] Well you throw
yourself with anything with a--
- As far as Mr. Alexander
Phipps is concerned,
he'll be left alone.
- [Tom] Permanently (laughs).
- Strictly alone.
And with the
greatest of pleasure.
- [Crow] More food, hide
the pain, more food.
Mmm, muenster.
- [Tom] The patio only
sees the sides a girl can
see from Brooklyn Heights, hey!
Whoa, the crazy--
- [Mike] Hey, the young
Milly Helper chronicles.
- Judy.
Is it about time you've
got dressed dear?
- I'm dressed.
- Well that's a
matter of opinion.
Go put on a dress
before they get here.
- Ah, for him?
Okay but nobody named Alexander
Phipps would ever notice
what I had on.
(car horn beeps)
- [Crow] Yeah, if you're
named Alexander Phipps,
it's just over for ya.
- [Tom] Wow, the
bacon truck is here.
- Jeepers!
Is he cool!
Really cool!
- [Crow] Tonight's
the night Mom!
- Mother!
They're here and look
at me, I'm a mess.
- Oh, why do you care, remember?
His name is Alexander Phipps.
- Oh, wait 'til I get that
brother of mine alone.
(bright music)
- [Tom] Jeez, it's
Chip and Dale.
- [Crow] Would you
just get in the door.
- Hi, Mom.
- [Tom] I'm back from the 20s.
- Gee it's good to be home.
- [Crow] Had to be
Robert McNamara.
- Mom, this is Alex.
- [Mom] Hello, Alex, we're
very happy to have you with us.
- Oh thank you Mrs. Adams,
it's nice of you to have me.
- [Crow] It's nice to be had.
- Wait a minute, don't tell me.
You're the twin
without the Tony.
- [Tom] Ah, go sit on
a carrot you crummy.
- Alex this is the little
sister I was telling you about.
Judy, Alexander Phipps.
- How do you do Mr. Phipps?
So nice you could come.
- Well thanks, Judy.
And the name is Alex.
- [Tom] Xander Phipps.
- Did you boys have your lunch?
- Oh no, we didn't want to
miss another one of your meals.
Besides, we wanted
to catch a shower.
- [Mike] Wow.
- Well okay, come along then.
I'll have everything ready
by the time you get back.
- [Crow] Join us
later if you want, Ma.
- Oh, Mom, how bout some of
those hot biscuits of yours?
- [Mike] Whoa, my God.
- All right, hot biscuits.
Judy will make them for you.
- Judy?
I didn't know she could--
- [Tom] Biscuit!
- Come on up.
- Oh, that sounds
real good, and thanks.
- [Crow] Hee, I'll
soap ya first!
- Mother, you do
the biscuits huh?
- Well it'll only take
you a moment Judy.
- Thanks Angel.
I think I will throw on a dress.
More lady like
don't you think so?
- Yes dear.
But Alexander Phipps
will never notice that.
- You're a doll mother.
- [Tom] Now make the biscuits.
- [Crow] You can hardly
see where you bit me.
- Sure do get a smooth shave
with this electric razor.
Hope your dad won't mind.
- [Bob] Nah, he
won't mind a bit.
He always lets me
use it when I'm home.
Dad's a swell guy,
you'll like him.
- [Tom] Just don't use his
razor, he goes ballistic!
- Hey, you're not running
out of hot water are you?
- What?
- I said you're not running
out of hot water are you?
I stayed under
quite a long time.
- [Mike] Wow.
- Oh don't worry about that,
wait 'til you see the electric
water heater dad got us.
We're loaded now, we have plenty
of hot water all the time.
- [Crow] Sounds fun, I
gotta get outta here.
- Hey, Bob.
- [Bob] Yeah?
- I thought you said your
sister was just a little kid?
- [Tom] She must be 40.
- [Bob] Don't let her fool ya.
She's still a little monster.
- [Mike] I'm the beast master.
- [Crow] There, now
I look like Mom.
Well thank goodness
for my electric dress.
- [Tom] Hey where's
the fire extinguisher?
- [Mike] He'll never touch
you Terry you're dirt.
- Hey, you look might purty.
- [Mike] In a Thelma
Retter sort of way.
- Now about that food.
- Food, is that all you can
think of at a time like this?
- [Crow] Ya mean lunchtime?
- Don't change the subject.
I ought to wring your
smug little neck.
- What's the matter
now, what have I done?
- Studious, serious minded.
- What are you talking about?
- Tops in all his classes.
- [Crow] Point, counter point.
- Now Judy, Alex
is really a guy--
- Who has little time for girls.
- Now wait a minute,
let me explain.
- And a woman hater to boot.
I think you're a stinker!
- [Crow] No, don't.
- Why do girls have
to have brothers?
- I love you too.
Now simmer down
sis, it's the truth.
- [Mike] What a loser
- Alex really has no time
for girls, especially you.
- Flattery will get you nowhere.
Just watch junior.
- [Mike] Doom, doom,
god I hate women.
Oh hi!
- Hi, Alex.
I know you're hungry.
You'll be eating in a jiffy.
Excuse me.
- [Crow] Ah, my new kidney.
Oh, one of them Insinkerators.
- [Mom] Everything's
ready, Judy.
- Come and get it.
(Tom imitates choking)
- [Crow] Hey, make
with the cha broads.
- Sit down boys.
- C'mon Alex, make
yourself at home.
- Sorry to put you to all
this trouble, Mrs. Adams,
but it does smell good.
- No trouble at all, Alex.
Everything's so easy
with an electric range.
Possibly I'm prejudice but seems
the food tastes better too.
- Say, I hate to corny
but what's cooking?
- Stew, beef stew.
Mom knows how you love it.
- Wonderful, it's
my favorite dish.
- [Mike] Well, used to be
my favorite dish, Jesus.
- [Crow] You got a claw
hammer or something I can
work on this with?
- Hot biscuits.
Mother made them.
- [Crow] Hey the electric phone!
- I'll get it Mom.
- Throw some of
these tomatoes on.
- Thanks.
- [Tom] Dad's calling
from Chippendales.
They got two shows,
he won't be home.
- More Similac dear?
- Did he arrive?
Man he's positively frantic.
- [Crow] He runs
around screaming.
- He's a real cool Jonah.
Tall, good looking,
nothing at all like the
drips around school.
- [Tom] If you'd like to
make a call please hang up--
- Uh huh.
And he drives a real
shafty convertible.
He really has it.
- [Tom] And I want it.
- Oh when he looks at me I get,
you know squishy.
- [Mike] Oh that's nice ma'am,
I'm just trying to
sell my magazines.
- This afternoon?
Oh that's a wonderful idea.
- [Crow] Have my way with him?
- What time?
Okay.
Bye!
- Well that stew was really
a production, Mrs. Adams.
Can we help with the dishes?
- Ah, no KT duty
around here, Sergeant.
- [Tom] We got dames to do that.
- Strictly automatic, see?
Oops.
- [Tom] Found the smell.
- Some in here already Mom.
- That's all right dear,
just put them in
with the others.
- [Crow] Why what are
all these gin bottles
doing in here?
- Oh wait a minute, Bob,
why not do it the easy way?
- [Tom] You're suffocating me.
- Excuse me, Mom.
- [Crow] It's Pepperidge Farm.
- That used to be
my job at home,
washing the dishes I mean.
- Oh, Bob and Judy have
had their share too.
But thank heaven, no
more wiping and wiping
dishes around here.
- [Crow] God your
hair smells terrific.
- And the dishwater
uses such hot water,
you couldn't possibly
put your hands in it.
- Sure, that makes the
dishes hygienically clean.
- I'll put the Heatwell cooker
in when I do the next load.
- [Crow] I've never felt so
comfortable with a
woman, Mrs. Adams.
Alexander please.
Do you want to have
breakfast sometime?
Don't do this to me Alexander.
- See, nothing to it is there?
- [Tom] And it's quiet too!
- [Crow] Eleanor, I'm busy
down here at the White House.
- Okay beautiful.
Now don't forget to
call me, will ya?
Right.
- [Crow] Good bye, Eleanor.
- Sally phoned and asked
me to go for a swim.
Thought you might
like to come along.
And bring Alex.
- Oh, thanks.
But I think Alex is
going to be busy.
- Busy doing what?
- Now look small fry,
don't give me any trouble.
All I know is he's
seeing a man at the
Northwest Machine Works on
the matter of hydraulics.
- [Tom] Say.
- Why don't you
ask him yourself?
- Thanks, I will.
- [Mike] I'm squishy and
I need to move on it.
- And the circulating air
completely dries them.
- [Crow] Please
stop I'm vulnerable.
- You certainly know
all about dishwashers.
- Oh not all, but to tell
the truth Mrs. Adams,
anything of mechanical or
electrical nature interests me.
Fits in with a hobby of mine.
- Dishwashers?
- Not exactly.
Time study.
Figuring out how to
do things better.
In less time and in less work.
- Time study.
Sounds interesting.
- Does going for a swim
sound interesting, Alex?
It's a swell day for it.
- Oh it is at that Judy,
well it'd be great but--
- [Tom] I find you repulsive.
- Can we make it
some other time?
I have an appointment
this afternoon
with an engineer.
As a matter of fact
that's one of the reasons
I came home with Bob.
- [Mike] One of the reasons.
- Hey I'd better hurry too.
Thanks for the
lunch, Mrs. Adams.
- [Tom] Just please go.
- And have a good swim, Judy.
- [Crow] Sure I will, homo.
(funky techno music)
- A lecture about mushrooms.
- [Crow] You're
dating Timothy Leary?
- Must be some mechanical
problem connected
with the lecture if
Alex wants to go.
- [Crow] God I
wish he'd go home.
Cockroach, sorry.
- Growing mushrooms under
artificial conditions.
Well after all the lecture
may be very interesting.
- Yes mother.
- [Crow] We should leave
the house sometime too.
- Mechanical stuff.
- [Crow] Mom.
- Time study.
- [Crow] Earth to mom.
- What did you say mother?
- Judy, I have an idea.
- Yes?
- I remember your father--
- [Tom] Vaguely.
- The trouble I had with him.
- [Tom] He was a thumb sucker.
- Seemed as if nothing
I did would interest
him until I--
- Until what, mother?
- [Crow] I got my tattoo.
- Well I discovered how
much he enjoyed good food.
- Oh.
- [Mom] Way to a
man's heart, Judy.
- Oh mother that's corny.
Everyone likes good food.
- I know dear but I'm thinking
of something else too.
- [Crow] Nude house work.
- And take a little conspiracy.
- [Judy] Conspiracy?
- A nice little conspiracy
for a nice young man.
- [Crow] Like white water.
- You remember I decided
not to go to the Guardian
Club dinner tomorrow night
because of Alexander's visit?
Well I've changed
my mind, I'm going.
- [Crow] The hell
with Alexander.
- You can find out for yourself
whether mother knows best,
now here's what we'll do.
- [Crow] Need some
rope, a chain saw,
potassium nitrate,
silver iodide.
Going on a man hunt, get me
a man, dee, dee, dee, dee.
Okay and thumbtacks and dun dun,
dun, dun, dun,
dun, dun, dun, dun.
Why I'm baking my panties but
that's what Mom suggested.
- [Tom] I'll turn it on now
but I'll light it later.
Here you go, Daddy.
Thanks kitten.
- Need anything
before I leave, Judy?
- I don't think so mother.
Now how long did you say it
would take this dinner to cook?
- Well let's see, your dinner
should cook for an hour
and a half at 350 degrees.
- Wait a sec, sweetie, let
me make with the mathematics.
I'm gonna dash over to Sally's,
she's gonna set my hair.
- It's almost three o'clock now.
You eat at 6:30 and your
dinner takes an hour
and a half to cook.
- [Crow] The Nazis
will be on you by then.
- Set the timer.
- [Crow] Timing bombs will
be tripped by the wires
when we drive through.
- And to cook for
an hour and a half.
- [Mike] Think they
forgot to stop filming.
- While I flip the set switch,
so it'll go on it automatically.
Turn the temperature dial to--
- [Crow] I think this is cool!
- 350 and I'm off
to Sally's, okay?
- Absolutely right.
- Oh, glad I remembered
to take the ham out of the
freezer this morning.
- [Tom] Is mom in
the Guardian Angels?
- I wish you weren't going out.
Do you think everything
will be all right?
- Of course darling,
it'll be lovely.
Now don't you worry, this
isn't the first meal you've
cooked you know.
- No, but it's the first
meal I ever cooked for Alex.
- [Tom] She's getting squishy.
- Well if I know Alex,
he'll be pleasantly
surprised and impressed.
I have to hurry dear,
I have things to do.
- What's a four letter
word for nuisance?
- [Crow] Standard sitcom
joke landing on runway seven.
- Oh that's easy.
J-u-d-y.
- Well, I'm off.
- Where you going, Mom?
- Can we give you
a lift Mrs. Adams?
- No thanks boys.
I don't know just what
time I'll be back tonight.
So I'm taking the car.
- Tonight?
What about dinner?
- Oh, Judy's taking
care of that.
- Judy?
Why Judy can't even boil
water without burning it.
Hey, maybe we better go
down to Hamburger Harry's,
at least we'll get
something to eat.
- Go right ahead
but you'll be sorry!
- Why I wouldn't think of
missing one of Judy's dinners.
- Thank you, Alex.
- [Tom] Let's get in
the car, let's go quick.
- You shouldn't
tease her so dear.
- Oh Mom, I was
only needling her.
- Well don't overdo it,
you'll give her the reds.
- [Crow] She's squishy,
she's got the reds,
what's going on around here?
- [Tom] Your mother's a freak.
- [Crow] Hash
brownies look good.
- [Tom] A young Mrs.
Lackhorn prepares dinner.
- [Crow] The Loretta Young show.
- That sounds interesting,
Alex, you know mushrooms
are big favorites of mine.
- [Mike] Shrooms!
- As I understand it,
there's quite an air
conditioning problem in.
- [Tom] Is this an
old coward play?
- Oh I don't think that would
be too much of a problem.
- [Crow] When are
you going home?
- You know--
- [Crow] That's what
I need, an idea.
Now to get my bustier
out of the freezer.
Has anyone noticed that
the daughter is psychotic?
- Well, you can always
give it a try, Mr. Adams.
- [Tom] What the, oh.
This is like Three Days of
the Condor, I trust no one
in this short.
Oh dear!
- Oh me.
- [Tom] Oh, did I call that?
- Dinner will be ruined.
- [Crow] Shut up the
men are talking in here.
- [Judy] Oh, I don't
know what I'll do.
- Excuse me sir,
lady in distress.
- [Mike] Heave to, my friend.
- [Alex] Trouble Judy?
Can I help?
- It's the mixer,
it just won't work.
- Oh let me take a look.
- [Tom] Talked to your
dad about mushrooms.
I think I impressed
the old fart.
- There we are.
- [Crow] God you're dumb.
- Plug slipped up, that's all.
- How you suppose that happened?
- Just one of those things.
The first thing you do when
an appliance doesn't work
is find out if it's plugged in.
That's the trouble
most of the time.
- Is that what time study is?
- No, but are you
interested in time study?
- Mother was telling
me that you're.
- It's a hobby of mine.
- [Tom] Set the hook.
- I'd love to hear about it.
- [Crow] Play 'em,
plenty of line.
- Take your kitchen.
Ever noticed anything about it?
- [Crow] Uh, it's a prison.
- There's the electric range.
The electric sink,
the garbage disposer,
the dishwasher, the
refrigerator, the freezer.
- Exactly, all wonderful helps.
Now here's something
you probably never
thought about Judy.
A kitchen today's like a
factory in a lot of ways.
- [Crow] Where's your upper lip?
- Product can only be good
if the right tools are used.
- [Crow] Yeah, but
your upper lip.
- Use the best machinery
that money can by.
- [Tom] Have you
considered braces?
- As a result, the
work is done faster,
better and easier.
Just as it is in
a modern kitchen.
See what I mean?
- Oh yes, and you're so
smart about all these things.
- Not really Judy it's just
that I'm interested and like
to make a study of it.
- [Tom] Now let's get
those clothes off.
- Now here's another thing.
Not only the best
tools are important,
but everything connected
with their use is
taken into consideration.
- [Crow] Don't wag your
finger at me pink boy.
- See how this works?
Just like machines in a factory.
- [Tom] He's heating up.
- Straight line production.
- [Tom] He's in the zone.
- They're not set this
way just for looks.
They're placed this way
for a definite purpose.
To save work, time
and unnecessary steps.
- Golly, I'm so impressed.
- [Mike] Needs to
meet a musician.
- It's called time
in motion study.
Come here.
- [Crow] Bring your sweet
behind over this way,
let me work on that zipper.
- Take your home freezer.
- [Tom] Get in.
- Full of fresh frozen foods.
Well there's a definite
saving of time and money.
- [Crow] And you
want to study this?
- And right next to it.
- [Crow] Don't tell me, I know.
- The refrigerator.
Keeps day to day food
in perfect freshness.
- [Tom] Now tell me
about the drapes.
- And the dishwasher, now
there's a machine that does
away with a chore
that everybody hates.
- [Crow] I did not know that.
- And again, right next to
it, the garbage disposal.
- [Tom] Put your arm in there
- Very convenient.
- [Mike] Bring your buns
over here sweet cheeks.
- The electric range.
- [Crow] Yeow!
- Automatically cooks, right?
And only a few steps from
where the food is kept.
- [Mike] So it's like
a normal kitchen?
- Notice how it all adds
up to one important thing?
- What?
- [Crow] Love.
- Consideration
for the housewife.
- [Crow] How does someone
become how you say a housewife?
- Even that mixer's
a big work saver.
- Oh god my whipped cream.
- [Crow] Oh just pour that
in there, that's right,
that's good that's
a bowl you know.
- Imagine having to do
that the hard way by hand.
- [Tom] Judy, beyond
thunder squishy.
- [Crow] Odd meatloaf, honey.
- Well I hope you brought
your appetite with you.
- Oh I certainly did sir.
The table looks beautiful, Judy.
- Oh thanks.
- Beautiful.
- [Crow] When are
ya leaving Alex?
- Here's to Judy.
- To Judy.
- [Mike] Judy, Judy, Judy.
- Well I brought along my
appetite too so let's sample it.
- [Alex] That's for me sir.
- How 'bout you Bob?
- [Bob] Oh, butt quick.
Just a small piece for
the boy at the end.
- [Tom] Well I'll try to
get through, Jesus Christ.
- A perfect dinner, Judy.
- [Crow] That's what
you shoulda cooked.
- And you said she couldn't boil
water without burning it.
- [Tom] You're a damned liar.
- Pineapple juice
chilled just right.
And that ham steak, oh brother.
- [Tom] Take me.
- Creamy potatoes,
buttered lima beans,
and that wonderful cherry
pie with whipped cream.
- [Bob] All right, all right.
- I think we oughta make
him eat all his meals
at Hamburger Harry's for that.
- [Mike] I'm not kidding this
is really exciting to me.
- Delicious meal Judy
and I'm very proud of ya.
- Yup Judy, you did all right.
- Thanks, but I can't
take all the credit.
Our kitchen does
everything but talk.
- [Mike] Oh delightful.
- About that lecture.
I don't know, after
such a wonderful meal,
I'd fall asleep at a lecture.
- [Mike] Oh boy here it comes.
- Maybe, how'd you
like to go dancing?
- Dancing?
Oh, Alex, how dreamy!
- Okay, well let's get
going on the dishes.
And Bob, you can take in
the lecture if you want.
- No thanks, I'll
watch TV tonight.
Lotta good shows.
- Now don't you young folks
worry about the dishes.
They're no trouble
around here, you know.
- Oh dad, you're a doll.
- [Crow] Actually I'm
being indicted but.
- Come on Alex.
- See ya later.
- Night.
- [Crow] Double bag it son.
- Here, let me give you
a hand with these, dad.
- Okay son.
- [Tom] Why don't I just
strap on some heels and a wig
the way I've been emasculated.
Mother's clipped me like
a gelding for god's sake.
- Oh, hello there.
- [Crow] Nice to see you?
- How'd it go, big success?
- Tremendous success.
We've got quite a
girl there, mother.
Quite a girl.
- [Mike] My lockjaw's back.
- What are those?
- [Crow] Nothing, nothing, oh.
- Wanna go with me?
Alex left them.
Something about
growing mushrooms
under artificial conditions.
- [Tom] And avoiding the narcs.
- I might find out how to
grow 'em in the basement.
Say I could move your laundry.
- Oh no you don't, uh uh.
Really Harry this is the end.
- [Mike] This film is brought
to you by the nerd council.
Support your local nerd.
- [Tom] The generous grant
from the Mom corporation,
the incredible power of Mom.
(gentle music)
- [Crow] So the point of this
short is that we should dabble
in mushroom growing.
- [Mike] Susan slept here.
(equipment whirring)
- Hum did hee hee.
- Hey Mike.
- Yeah.
- I figured out it would
be a lot more convenient
for all of us if you moved
the mads light over to the
left a little.
- Okay, all right.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Back, back, just a little
bit, back, back, back.
Nudge, just a nudge.
Little more, inch more,
inch more, teensy, teensy,
baby steps the whoa stop.
Ooo, weird.
- Bad news, Mike, our theme
song tested rather poorly
and well I'm a big time
executive and I made
a snap decision.
We're going to start our
own radio station and we're
going to name it Frank.
- A radio station called Frank?
- That's right so come on.
Turn your crank to Frank.
- Less talk.
- And more new country.
- Winona.
- Billy Rae Cyrus.
- Love that Frank.
- Okay.
- Yeah, you know I can't
promise that I personally will
be turning my crank
to Frank but I--
- But it's a radio
station called Frank.
- More Garth.
More Reba.
- Winona.
(all grumbling)
- Brooks and Dunn.
- I don't even know about--
- Brooks and Dunn!
- Winona.
- What is Winona?
- I don't know.
- Don't you see how great it is?
My name is Frank.
The radio station's
name is Frank.
It's totally uncharacteristic
to name a radio station Frank.
- More Garth, more Reba.
- Winona.
- Am I out of Reba?
Do I need more Reba?
- Or any Winona?
- I don't know sorry guys,
gotta think about this one,
turning my crank, I don't think.
(gentle techno music)
(tense music)
- [Tom] I don't
know who Reba is.
Ah, yes the Bobby Knight story.
- [Mike] Well the Inquisition
were violent years.
- [Crow] And your crusades.
- [Tom] Oh the Hun years too.
- [Mike] The 30 years war.
- [Tom] How long was that war?
- [Mike] It was about.
- [Crow] New York City,
the city that never moves.
Is there a Parkins vibe in this.
Poor Carl Parkins, he
had brown suede shoes,
he was so close.
- [Tom] So is this
the naked city?
- [Crow] It's the
scantily clad city.
- [Tom] I did it again.
- [Crow] Zing!
Are you quite finished?
Uh oh, the movie has a
surgeon general's warning.
- [Mike] Well they should never
have used a manual Francisco
on this movie an electric
one would be so much better.
- [Tom] Traffic is hardly
moving on the bridge tonight.
- [Crow] Victor most of
California except Lompoc.
- [Mike] Okay.
- [Crow] The thick chalk
years, everyone forced to write
with the Palmer method.
Well I gotta go buy some
drugs and insult some people
and abandon my
parents and friends.
- [Mike] That's straight from
Thomas Paine, by the way.
- [Crow] Well let's not forget
adequate support garments.
- [Narrator] This is
a story of violence.
A violence born of the
uncontrolled passions of
adolescent youth and nurtured
by this generation of parents.
- [Crow] The devil
made me do it!
- [Narrator] In their own
smug little world of selfish
interests and confused ideas
of parental supervision
refused to believe
today's glaring headlines.
- [Mike] The name's Friday.
- [Narrator] But
it has happened.
Only the people and places
have been given other names.
- [Tom] Courtney Love.
- [Crow] Hey, how bout a
little sugar for the father
of my country huh?
I will not tell a lie.
- [Tom] God my teeth
hurt, thank you!
Ba boom!
- [Mike] His office is
just off the cafeteria.
- [Tom] Just dropped a
hell of a turd in there
if you know what I mean.
- [Mike] Oh, Judge Joe.
- [Crow] Let's hear
it for your headliner.
- Remain seated
and come to order.
Court is now in session.
The honorable Raymond
Clara judge presiding.
- [Crow] Fake court
will now begin.
- Will you approach
the bench please?
- [Tom] But don't touch it
it's made out of styrofoam.
- [Crow] Um, have you got a five
I could borrow til tomorrow?
- It's always difficult
for an old friend to sit in
judgment of an old friend.
- [Crow] But you're
going down man.
- But law is law and it
must be administered to one
as to another.
- [Tom] Do your worst ya puss.
- It now comes to
light that both of you
over the past 18
years have proven
yourselves utterly incompetent.
- [Crow] Thank you.
- Of the most important
responsibility given
to a man and his wife.
- [Crow] Sir, it's
one parking ticket.
- I refer to the
bringing up of children
in your own home.
- [Mike] Honey, don't laugh.
- In all fairness to the
society which you so miserably
failed an injustice
to this child,
I must deny your request.
- [Crow] By the way,
you're ugly and stupid too.
- How am I to blame?
Where could I have failed?
I remember I gave her
everything she ever wanted.
- [Crow] Huh, her neck
is having a flashback.
- [Mother] Everything.
- [Mike] Ladies and gentlemen
your screenwriter, Ed Wood.
- Hi, Mom.
- [Crow] Can I have
more of everything?
- Got time to talk a minute,
it's rather important.
- Good gracious no.
I'm an hour late already.
- [Tom] I'm two weeks late.
- Gotta be first and all
that sort of thing you know.
Besides, what can be so
important in your young life
as to warrant my
attention so drastically?
- [Crow] Wow.
- Well its been a long
time since we've had a
heart to heart talk.
- There there, it can wait.
- [Crow] Go away.
- Besides, what can be more
important than our charities?
So many children
and needy families.
- [Crow] Really
bugs me you know.
- We're so busy
this time of year
and it's very very important.
- I guess you're right mother.
- Of course I am.
- [Crow] Now go do some crimes.
- Thank you darling.
Tell you a secret.
- [Tom] I hate you.
- I think I like it
down a the club so much
'cause I keep getting
such nice flattery.
The girls are always
saying, my, my,
how young and pretty you look.
- [Crow] For an old hag.
- With an 18 year old daughter.
- But you are pretty mother.
- Oh go along with you,
but it does sound good.
Got a date tonight?
- Well sort of.
- Oh you pretty one
of course you do.
But then what night
lately haven't you?
- [Tom] Watch 227.
- You come in as late
as you have been,
do be careful and
not make any noise.
- Dad?
- Oh don't get me wrong,
he hasn't complained
or said anything.
- [Mike] In fact he
hasn't moved in a week.
- The poor man works so hard.
That newspaper will
be the death of him.
- [Crow] His route
is killing him.
- Do be a dear and take
care when you come in.
He needs what little
rest he can get.
- [Tom] It got rough last night.
- Thank goodness you aren't
one of those character
types that your father's paper
is always printing about.
Need some mad money?
Or is he a gentleman?
- I have enough mother.
- Don't be silly.
There's never enough.
- [Tom] Please, no more, not
again, my life is hell enough,
no more money.
- You left the
amount blank again.
I could be mean and fill
it in for a fortune.
- You could.
But you won't.
Let me know how much you
make it out for so that I can
keep my bank balance straight.
- All right mother, will you
be using my car again tonight?
- If you don't mind dear.
- You can use mine.
- Now I'll tell you a secret.
- [Mike] This
doesn't make sense.
- There are times I
like yours better.
Tonight is one of those times.
- [Crow] Keep your life
to yourself, honey.
One google plex and 79 cents.
My life is hell, how much
more of this can I take?
I'm going to report her
to child protection.
- [Phil] Hello?
- Phil?
This is Paul.
- [Tom] Paul?
- Is everything ready?
- [Crow] Who is this?
- Good.
Did Gerry show yet?
- [Crow] Paul.
- Stop worrying,
they'll get to you.
- [Tom] But I don't know any--
- I'll be along as
soon as I get dressed,
mother just this minute left.
- [Tom] Well who's Paul,
I don't know, hello?
- [Crow] Think I'll throw
pigs blood on the wall.
Think of the hellish life.
Your mother writing
a blank check.
- [Tom] But does that
justify going out
and making right turns?
No I say to you.
- [Crow] Society owes
me a Kit Kat bar.
Rosewood Super Service, soon
to be Rosewood Lickety Lube.
- [Tom] Every minute away
from my porno mags is hell.
Good evening, it's my
pleasure to serve, hey!
- [Crow] Benice Arbuto
is holding him up.
(suspenseful music)
There's a free oil filter
and fill up if that.
Hey do we want the
Ridgid tool calendar?
Oh, left turn.
- [Tom] You can
trust our octanes.
Check your hoses.
Need an area map, we got plenty.
- [Mike] Hello girls, good
luck with the hold up.
- [Crow] Saw your mom
in here the other day.
- [Tom] Let's go we got all
the barrel of fun snacks.
- [Crow] Please take
an air freshener.
I'll just go ahead
and fall then.
Hey, your rear tire's a little
low, ding ding, ding ding.
Was the restroom clean?
(funky techno music)
- [Mike] Well I did a
C-section but I was unable
to find anything.
- Will he pull through doc?
- He hasn't regained
consciousness and he's top
heavy odds if he ever will.
- Pretty bad, huh?
- Pretty bad.
- These fool kids,
when will they learn?
- These aren't kids,
these are morons.
- [Tom] Will he ever pump again?
- Hi, Bernie.
- Lieutenant, Tom, Doctor.
- [Crow] Honey, Pete, Cookie.
- Another one, eh?
- Pretty bad one this
time, how 'bout it doc?
- Pretty bad.
I'll get back to you later
if there's any change.
- [Mike] Said he'd give
me a deal on wiper blades.
- Anything I can print?
- You heard the doctor, nothing.
- Suppose it's the same gang?
- Chances are.
- If only he comes
to then we'll be--
- Well if it is the same gang
it brings their record to 17.
- And the last seven of
'em have been gas stations.
- [Mike] Any pattern?
- Looks like they'll make
a specialty of gas stations
for awhile now.
- If they do we may
be ready for them.
- How do you mean?
- [Crow] Well we'll
prepare ourselves.
- All gas stations open after
10PM will be warned to have
two men on duty at all times.
One of those men
could be a policeman.
- [Tom] Well I tried to jump
start him, that didn't work.
- Lieutenant, I left
Dr. Ryan in charge.
The man was lucky,
he'll pull through.
- [Crow] Well let's just
let the scene peter out.
All but the two tonic
races will never be capable
of leadership and yet
they breed rapidly
like the mongrels that
they, oh, more later.
- Hi, chief.
- Oh, hello Barnie.
- [Crow] Where's
your big purple suit?
- Oh I'm tired but
no more than you.
- [Mike] I mean you
look really bad.
- Too much to
newspapers these days.
Haven't seen my daughter
Paula in a week.
- I ran into her up at
school earlier this week.
- [Crow] Well stalked her.
- She gets more
beautiful everyday.
- Like I said, I wouldn't know.
One of these days I'm
gonna take a day off,
maybe get to know her again.
- [Crow] Nah, who am I kidding?
- What happened down
at the hospital?
- The gas station
attendant pulled through.
- [Mike] Good, I need gas.
- He'll spend a couple
more weeks in the hospital
but he'll live.
- How much could he tell?
- It was the same gang.
Four of 'em, wore masks,
Levi's, leather jackets.
- [Mike] Looked
like your daughter.
- With a handful of guns.
- Same bunch.
Probably the same clues.
- [Mike] Who's that
on the wall, Chopin?
- Well no finger prints.
55 sedan, license unknown,
masks, caps covering their hair,
same old routine.
- Well, our little gang has
one thing in their favor.
- Yeah, what's that?
- They haven't
killed anyone, yet.
- That's not their fault,
they've tried hard enough.
Just give 'em a
little more time.
- It's too bad we can't
do anything about giving
them a little more time.
However, they happen to be news.
- [Mike] Thank you Ben Bradley.
- You stick with the
police department.
See this thing through.
- [Crow] I'm going
back to sleep.
- You're the boss, chief.
- [Crow] We gotta get
this story out by,
oh next week is fine.
- [Tom] Those Etruscans are
drawing even nearer, I smell.
(bright music)
- [Crow] Hey, that's the
same right turn as before.
Tom McCahill says the big
55 Caddy rides smooth.
- [Tom] Oh the passion,
I find you so acceptable.
Here comes the Paige
Kavanaugh trio.
- [Mike] They're
on display, hmm.
- [Tom] They parked
under the RKO logo.
- [Crow] Oh you're smoldering
averageness, stop me.
You gonna kiss her?
You are acceptable as
a mate, take me now.
- [Woman] Ain't love something?
- Well what is this?
Johnny, who are they?
- Don't ask so many questions,
you might find the answers.
- [Crow] That's true, but
how does that apply here?
How?
- Gerry, be careful.
That's a beautiful sweater.
- [Crow] Why thank you.
Take it off.
- What are you talking about?
- You ain't got
stuffing in your ears.
Take that sweater off.
- By what right do you--
- Shut up and do like she says.
- Do what they say,
Cheryl, they've got guns.
- Yes, Shirley, we've got guns.
- [Mike] The Peggy Noonan Gang.
- You're very observant
for a pretty boy.
For god's sake Cheryl,
take the sweater off,
give it to her.
- [Tom] Got this
down at Fallbush's,
they got it in six sizes!
- Now buster, it's your turn.
Step out.
- [Crow] I'd just like to
say I'm totally amenable to
taking off any clothes
you want oh my oh.
- Turn around.
Put your hands out
in front of you.
Lean forward and put your
hands on the car door.
C'mon, c'mon we
haven't got all night.
You've seen this done before.
- [Crow] Take off
your underwear without
taking off your pants.
- [Mike] I really think you
need to spank me I've been bad.
- [Crow] Whenever
I get to the end
I fall into a wormhole, sorry.
- A lousy 11 bucks.
You characters oughta
learn to carry more dough.
- You can stand up now.
- [Crow] And take
my pants off right?
- Maybe he's got more
to offer than his money.
- What are you getting at?
- [Crow] I got a
Jerry Garcia tie.
- Big, strong, little
pretty maybe but.
- Yeah, under conventional
circumstances he could
be very interesting.
- Why wait for
conventional circumstances?
- [Crow] Why indeed, yes.
- You've got a point there.
What about her?
- Oh tie her up and toss her
in the back of this heap.
- [Mike] Tough luck, honey, gee.
- Tie her up?
- You heard me.
- Sure I heard you but
maybe you'd like to tell
me what I'd use to
tie her up with?
- [Crow] I got some
rope in the trunk.
- Use the skirt, that
looks strong enough.
Tear it and use it.
- You heard her
girl, get a move on.
- [Tom] Sorry but
this is so great.
- [Mike] I completely
condone what you're doing.
- Now back to you handsome.
- Look, you have my money.
You have my watch
you have my ring.
What more do you want?
- [Crow] Oh we'll be going
out again real soon Rick.
- [Tom] See this works as
a nice matching cuff too.
- Toss her in the
back of this heap.
- Okay, but do you mind
telling me where we're going?
- Some place where it's
safe, just follow us.
- [Crow] Dr. Forester has
sent us a truly great movie.
- [Tom] Rabbit goes around
the feet, through the thing.
- [Crow] Now could you switch
the radio station please?
- [Mike] She'll probably
be okay, bye honey.
- [Crow] Don't wait up honey,
I'm doing this for you!
- [Mike] Now if all four
of ya have to get involved
I understand it could get
rough and that's fine I.
- [Tom] Third day in a
row with him this has
happened I'm beginning
to suspect something.
- [Crow] A fantasy will
never satisfy her again.
- [Mike] I beg of you
don't lightly kiss my belly
and then don't nibble at my
nipple buds and don't drag
your shiny hair across my
body because I hate that!
There's a spot behind my
ear, please don't kiss there.
$11 went a long way back then.
- [Tom] Girls, can I see
your park permit, oh my god.
- [Crow] Okay, squeal piggy.
What a great movie,
we gotta get gypsy,
she's gotta see this.
- [Tom] Wormholes again.
- [Crow] Penthouse Forum,
the motion picture.
Oh, tattle tail, jeez.
Okay honey, I'll
meet you at home!
Refuses to file charges.
- [Mike] Says thank you thank
you thank you thank you.
- [Tom] Hundreds of men
flock to crime scene.
They took turns atoning
and there was four of them.
(suspenseful music)
(funky techno music)
- [Announcer] Ladies
and gentlemen,
Ester
Hoffman
Howard.
- Wanna
look at you.
I could learn how I
can't, I can't, I can't.
Oh no I can't do it.
No, no, no.
Oh no!
Woo!
(wildly cries)
(wildly screams)
Wee!
(laughs wildly)
Are you watching me now?
Who watched closely now?
(alarm rings)
Don't know where.
It's movie time, where?
(equipment whirring)
- [Tom] Good news,
Streisand killed.
- Don't tell me that you're
going to have breakfast again.
- No, I'll get
something else later.
- You won't forget
about the party tonight?
- [Crow] Party?
- What party?
- See, I knew you
wouldn't remember.
When I told you,
Paula's birthday party.
- [Mike] Paula, who's Paula?
- I did forget, well
it's impossible for me,
I've got a newspaper to get out.
With these young
hoodlums running rampage
through the town,
I'm kept pretty much on the go.
Especially at night,
that's when they work.
Who knows when or where
they'll strike again.
- Sometimes you sound
more like a policemen
than a newspaper man.
- Sometimes there
isn't much difference.
- That is too bad.
- I can't be here either.
She's having a pajama
party this year.
- What in the world
is a pajama party?
- Oh, they all sit
around, play games dressed
in their pajamas.
- [Crow] Oh tonight tonight.
- No boys invited.
- Oh I see.
- We're having our charity
bazaar tonight and I'm the duly
elected chairman of
the sales committee.
I've just got to be there.
- Well, Paula's old enough
to take care of herself now.
I'll get a little
gift this afternoon,
have one of the boys
from the office drop
by with it tonight.
- Oh, she'll like that.
Paula's such an
understanding child.
- [Mike] Well goodbye my
suffocating little ice queen.
- See you when I can.
- [Crow] Is that
fake enough for ya?
Yup I'm really off
to the newspaper,
I'm certainly not going
to that spot where
they attacked that fellow, no.
Freedom, ah!
- [Tom] Hello, did you
have an appointment?
- Happy birthday, darling.
- Thanks Mom.
- You were out late
again last night.
- A little.
- I can tell.
Your eyes don't sparkle
the way they should.
Do you feel ill?
- No, just a little tired.
- A good breakfast
will fix you up.
What would you like
to have this morning?
- [Crow] A blank check.
- Please don't bother.
I'm just not hungry.
- Now, now, mother knows best.
You're a growing girl,
you need your
vitamins for strength.
Now you just sit there and
I'll get you something.
It'll only take a
minute, it's all ready.
You have plenty of
time before school.
- [Tom] Oh sure those cheerful
morning words and tender
pat on the cheek meant
to hurt and scar.
- [Crow] Another classic walk
across the living room scene.
Freedom!
- [Tom] Honey,
here's your SlimFast.
- [Crow] I coulda
sworn I had a daughter.
I drive everyone away
with my affectionate
good natured demeanor.
- [Mike] Sign up here for
volunteer stake out duty.
- [Crow] Da, da, da,
da, da, da, da, da, da.
Got big plans for
the government,
why has the Lord chosen
me you might ask?
- Paula!
What in the world
brings you down here?
- Hi dad.
Been so long since
I've seen you I thought
I'd drop in today.
It's my birthday you know?
- Happy birthday!
- [Crow] Now get out.
- Gee honey I'm sorry I can't
be at your party tonight,
but you know how busy I am.
- I understand dad.
But then you wouldn't
look good at an all girl
pajama party now would you?
- Well this certainly
is a surprise.
- I thought it would be.
- [Crow] I'm Paula,
your daughter.
- Why aren't you in school?
- No classes 'til 1:30
and extra long lunch hour.
- Oh, I see.
- [Tom] What's this rag, oh.
- Have they got a line on
the girls that did this yet?
- Now don't you bother your
pretty little head about such
things that's your
dad's department.
- It could be very
important to me.
- [Dad] How do you mean?
- [Crow] You know, significant.
- Well I'm up for president
of the student body
this year and this
type of thing you call
juvenile delinquency
could help me
if I knew more about it
and how to prevent it.
- If you knew how to prevent it,
you'd go down in history as the
greatest person of our time.
- [Crow] After Casey
Stingle of course.
- But that is commendable.
- I figure it this way dad.
You're on the inside, you
know the real low down almost
as soon as it happens.
- I guess you're
right about that.
But what is it
you want me to do?
- That's easy.
As soon as anything
happens, you tell me.
- [Dad] Everything?
- Everything.
- [Crow] There's a 10
spot in it for you.
- Are you older?
- So what, it's not
too big for you.
I hardly catch you at
home anymore so I'll have
to see you here.
- [Crow] Ouch.
- Well, if it'll help
you to be president,
I'll do it.
- Dad, you're a peach.
Now anything new on
last night's bunch?
- Have you read the paper?
- Yes.
- Then you have the story.
- Honest?
- Honest.
- [Mike] Come on you like
Cappy Dick for god's sake.
- Either the girls have no
previous record or they're
from out of town.
It's Lieutenant Holmes
theory that they were from
out of town.
- [Crow] No we weren't.
- The boy couldn't
identify any of them from
the police picture files.
And there it will stay until
something else turns up.
- What about the gas station
affair, is there anything
new on that?
- [Tom] Say please.
- Nothing you could call new.
Four young boys.
- [Crow] The Dave Clark five?
- Holmes is putting a
policemen in mechanics clothes
with each gas station staying
open after 10 at night.
If the gang tries another
gas station heist,
they'll be all through.
- [Mike] I must see
the liquor stores.
- Well that's interesting
enough for a starter.
- [Mike] Oh, by the way,
have they built any
7/11's around here?
- Bye!
- [Crow] What a neat kid.
Wish I had a daughter like her.
(bright music)
- [Mike] Come on girls,
let's spin donuts on
the football field.
Oh my pits hurt.
- Calling off the
gas station jobs.
- Oh, we can't
call off Clanton's.
- We already have.
- But why?
We could have had more
of a ball at Clanton's
than all the rest put together.
- Maybe it'd be a little
too much excitement,
even for us.
The cops have pulled a sneak.
They'll be waiting for us.
- So what, how can the cops
know we picked Clanton's?
- I'll explain later.
The main thing is they know.
Puts an end to our gas
station jobs for awhile.
We'll have to think
up something else.
- [Crow] I hate robbing retail.
- I wanna get back
at Principal Bates.
- She have you on
the carpet again?
- Yeah, the old witch.
- What'd you do this time?
- Practically nothing.
- [Tom] Killed a cop.
- Nothing for them to
get so hep up about.
Just that math.
Teacher flunked me
again so I told her off.
I'd like to get even
with all of them.
- Maybe you'll get
the chance then.
We'll have to go over to
Sheila's tomorrow and get
rid of last week's loot.
- [Tom] We hear and obey.
- [Crow] We hear and obey.
- How come we don't use
your car on our jobs?
How come your
mother's all the time?
- My car would be
spotted a mile away.
Let's get in.
- [Tom] By the way we're
all pregnant from the
guy we attacked.
- [Mike] Ah yes the scene
that was condemned by the
Catholic league of America.
- [Tom] But I want
to rob Clanton's.
Hello, hmm?
They arrived in a U-boat.
- [Mike] They're all
standing up in that car.
Oh, they have to pick
up Mimi Van Doren.
- [Crow] That'd be hard.
Oh phooey, it says
no solicitation.
Well, back in the car.
Okay, let's rob the entire
apartment building instead.
- [Mike] Did anybody
remember the potato salad?
- [Crow] So is this
that Melrose Place
everyone's been talking about?
- [Mike] I know they dress
as men so they can live
in this apartment building.
(door rings)
- [Crow] Walk like a
man, talk like a hello.
- [Tom] Well I don't know who
you are or why you're here
but come on in.
- [Crow] Sal Minnio
entertains at home.
- You kids have been lucky!
- So what?
- Maybe we're just
a little smart.
- Just be careful you
don't get too smart
for your own good.
- [Tom] A double pleasure
is waiting for you.
- Help yourselves
if you want any.
- I'll get some.
- [Crow] Well, you look good.
- What have you go
this time, more junk?
- We've never
brought you junk yet.
- Couldn't get back half
of what I paid you for
that last mess.
- Yeah, losing your money
gets you a setup like this?
- [Mike] Isn't that
Harpo on the right there?
- Just as I thought, junk.
- Those are real diamonds,
I had them appraised.
- Appraised?
Well that was kind
of foolish wasn't it?
You could be caught
if they were traced.
- What do you take
me for a stoop?
- [Tom] No, a porch.
- Jimmy the fence
looked 'em over,
he offered me $200 for
the bracelet alone.
- $500 for the lot.
- I think we'll take
our business to Jimmy.
- [Crow] Ah the
free market at work.
- Come on gang, Sheila
doesn't want to be bothered
with us anymore.
- [Tom] Let's take our
air fresheners elsewhere.
- You're a bunch
of blackmailers.
- Oh not that big yet,
but give us a chance.
We're still growing.
- [Crow] We like
milk and it shows.
- Did you really
see Jimmy this time?
- What difference does it make?
We got what we wanted.
I'm not interested in the money.
There's plenty of that at home.
It's the principle of the thing.
I don't want anyone
getting the idea they can
put something over on me.
Sheila'd take her right teeth
and then try to steal the rest.
It's the thrill that gets me.
The thrill of the chase maybe.
- [Crow] Oh and
shopping, I like to shop.
Goodness I like Squirt.
- [Mike] Ugh, here
comes Uncle Maim.
- 750.
You think you're
pretty smart don't you?
- I don't think I know.
That's why I'm the
leader of this pack.
- You're a punk or you
wouldn't be tied up in this
small time penny ante business.
- You got better ideas?
- Maybe.
- Speak your piece.
- [Crow] Or forever
hold your now.
- You girls take the bottle
into the bedroom for awhile.
I want to talk to
Paula privately.
- [Crow] Uh, which
one of us is Paula?
- And close the door.
- [Mike] Beat it Harpo.
- Start talking.
- [Tom] I just
wanted to tell you
how much I love your outfit.
- What do you
think about school?
- What are you driving at?
- I've got a connection
that doesn't like schools.
- [Crow] Chester,
the third-grader.
- Most kids don't.
- We're not talking kid talk.
It's worth a lot of money
to a certain organization
if certain damages are reported.
- I don't get it.
- You don't have to.
All you have to know is,
if you can wreck a
few school rooms,
you can make yourself and
your pack a load of dough.
- How much dough?
- More than you can use.
Besides, you've always
said the money means
nothing to you.
- Why would anyone pay just
to have schools wrecked?
- That's none of your
business or mine.
I have the connection.
And besides, there'll be a
great throw behind this move.
And don't worry if a few flags
get destroyed in the process.
- [Tom] Not Old Glory!
- Let's just say it's part of
a well organized foreign plan.
- [Crow] Communism!
- I don't understand.
- You don't have to!
All you have to do
is what you're told.
- [Mike] Now go to your room.
- How soon do we move?
- Just as soon as you
can but be careful
you're not caught.
You're not good to
me in the clink.
- We won't get caught.
- I don't know how
you can be so sure.
- [Crow] I wear Secret.
- It's easy.
- [Mike] This is one of the
rough spots in the dialectic.
Oh, Pete Hammel's place.
- [Tom] They love
this song, don't they.
- [Crow] Oh look
at those pajamas,
she may as well be nude.
- [Mike] Oh, the pajama party.
- [Crow] I could
use a hand here.
All right who's next?
- [Mike] They'll strip in the
woods for a total stranger
but they're modest
in their own home.
- [Crow] Now there's a girl
who takes squishiness and does
something about it.
- [Mike] I think
we're out of s'mores.
- [Tom] His pajamas
are a little formal.
You ever thought of the
advantages of owning a truly
fine set of encyclopedias?
- [Crow] I wouldn't
invite Ralph Bellamy
to my slumber party.
- [Tom] Thursday,
Friday, happy days.
- [Crow] Your zipper
seems to be stuck.
- Sheila talks too much.
- All she did was say
that you're a right guy
and that I should meet you.
And as pretty as you
are, I'm glad I came.
- I don't need her to
pick my friends for me.
- [Crow] Or my nose.
- I'm sure you don't.
- I'm pretty particularly.
- Well I'm sure you are.
- I've played it
alone for a long time.
- [Mike] Sure you have.
- That's how I plan to keep it.
- Maybe you should look for
my new company elsewhere?
- No.
You're here now you
might as well stay.
- Okay, since I'm
now an invited guest,
you won't mind my giving
you a birthday gift?
- Hmm?
- [Tom] No I've already
got one of these,
do you have a receipt
so I can return it?
- [Crow] Oh heck
what's one more.
(lively horn music)
- [Mike] Do anything but lay
off of my blue suede shoes.
- [Crow] Pajamas,
jazz and communism.
This is wild!
- [Mike] Oh he's making
out with Erin Moran!
- [Tom] Someone's
dancing with Otis.
- [Crow] Skin, I see skin!
- [Mike] Take it easy.
- [Crow] Nope, it's gone.
Masters and Johnson, we've
got some advice for you.
- [Mike] Makeout police,
come out with your lips up.
Hi, ya ready?
- Yeah?
- I'd like to speak
to Miss Parkins.
- Paula?
- Yes.
- What about?
- [Crow] Vinyl siding.
- I don't think that's
any of your affair.
- Why you.
- It's all right Manny.
He's from my dad's office.
- [Crow] Go ahead and punch him.
- Fine way to greet a
guest who bears gifts.
A mud butler.
- Don't pay Manny
a second thought,
he's seen too many
gangster movies.
He's really very nice
once you get to know him.
- That brings up the point,
do many people stick around
long enough to get to
know him that well?
- [Mike] Quit needling me.
- May I come in?
- Sure, if you want to.
- [Mike] Just let me
explain the mud butler joke,
see a mud butler is a thing
that is placed on the ground,
bolted and then you
scrape the mud off your,
you're not buying it.
- [Crow] Well, grab yourself
a guy, I'll see if I can
find you a nightie.
- [Tom] I brought an extra lap.
- I see the party's
formal dress.
- It's a pajama party.
- [Mike] I was joking again.
- Yeah I can see that
but mixed crowd, huh?
- Well uh, gang, I want you
to meet my father's star
reporter Barnie Stetson.
- [Crow] Pajama party beat.
- Hi gang!
- [Mike] L7 man.
What?
- Look, don't let me
interrupt anything,
birthdays are just
like Christmas,
they only come once a year.
- [Crow] There is
an audible thud
every time he tells a joke.
- [Mike] What am I
alone in here, hello?
- It's kinda cold in
here all of a sudden.
- [Mike] Again a joke, uh.
- [Tom] I like to smoke,
do you like to smoke?
- That's a cute pair.
- They have their points.
- Oh, almost forgot the
reason for my visit.
You're father's gonna
be very late tonight
and asked me to drop
this off for you.
- Poor dad, works so hard.
Thanks for bringing it.
- Aren't you gonna open it?
- Later.
I know what it is.
Dad gets me the same
present every birthday.
- [Mike] A really little car.
- A new watch.
And Mom, come look.
- Ah nevermind Paula.
I saw the new convertible
when I came in.
- It never changes.
Mom and Dad haven't been to
my birthday parties in years.
But always the same presents.
Mom sneaks out and takes
my old car in for a trade
then has a new one
delivered secretly.
Takes a cab to her club.
Funny, I like her sedan better.
- [Tom] I have a really
funny line here but I'm
afraid to use it.
- Let's have some more music.
(funky techno music)
- [Mike] I love ya Ada Annie.
- Ain't you seen
enough yet, sob sister?
Maybe you've seen enough
to know you ain't wanted.
- Knock it off Manny.
- I don't like this guy's looks.
- [Tom] Excuse me I do.
- Why don't you
change 'em Manny?
- Maybe that's a good idea.
What about I should change
your looks sob sister?
- [Crow] Mud butler, sob
sister, mud butler, sob sister.
- How old are you punk?
- Over 21.
- Now that's old enough.
- [Mike] Wanna go out some time?
- [Tom] Thanks for
stopping by, Ted.
- He asked for that.
- [Crow] I'm trying to think
of a quip or something here.
- You're in bad company Paula.
But I don't wanna sound like
I'm telling you your business.
- Then don't try.
- [Crow] Well I'll see ya
next year with your new watch.
- [Tom] How'd you guys
like that scene, hmm?
- [Mike] It's something
you wipe your boots on
so it's an insult, forget it.
- [Crow] This is gonna be
the front page story in
the Glen View Shopper
Change me oh.
- [Mike] We got trouble
right here in River City.
- Why that dirty sob sister
I'll take care of him.
- Haven't you had
enough for one night?
- [Crow] This is one
of the worst planned
pajama parties ever.
- Good night boys,
the parties over.
- [Mike] Don't hate me Susan.
- But the night's
just beginning.
- [Crow] And that
goes double for me.
- [Mike] Oh boy I hope they
show another right turn.
(suspenseful music)
- [Crow] Ha, they
backed up the whole way.
- [Mike] That's very
good you scored a 94
on your driver's test.
- [Crow] Bump, oh no you hit
the crew and he's really mad.
- [Mike] Let us in we've
gotta make fruit fly medium.
- This is something I've been
waiting for a long long time.
- We'll get it done as
quickly as possible.
We'll get in, get the
job done and get out.
- [Mike] Isn't that sort of
a general rule with a crime?
- [Crow] I hope they
kill Miss Ducato.
- I'm going to smash
everything in this joint.
- Let's do it quick
and get out of here.
- [Crow] They're gonna bring
the fifth grade to its knees!
- I hate you!
- [Crow] Stupid
inanimate objects.
- I wish this was
your scrawny neck.
- [Mike] Good, good
you're letting it all out,
now what if both your
parents were here?
Oh no, no, not that no!
- I'll hate you
til the day I die.
- [Crow] And I'm not
gonna clap the erasers.
- [Tom] I'm making
over $1.75 an hour.
- [Mike] But this is
actually encouraged
in open schools.
So how is this lucrative
for them again?
- [Crow] I don't understand.
Girl gang goes on rampage.
President Eisenhower declares
a state of detention.
- [Tom] Down with the globe!
- [Crow] Mrs.
Hathaway goes berserk.
- [Mike] This is for you Betsy
Ross you stupid little hoe.
(police sirens blaring)
- [Tom] Later, in completely
unrelated footage.
- [Crow] Well if it's
that denuding girl gang
I better go in alone.
- You've all got guns,
get 'em into action.
- [Mike] Just confess to
tipping the desks over,
take your chances.
(gun fire rings)
- They're shooting back!
- What do you expect them
to do, throw powder puffs?
- Our ammunition
can't last forever.
- How many have you all got?
- Well what's in my gun.
- All I've got
left is in my gun.
- I got 10 shells in my pocket.
We'll have to beat
it to the car.
- [Crow] I've got gum.
- I've got a dozen boxes
under the back seat.
Lay it into 'em fast
then we'll beat it.
- [Mike] They need
to ask themselves
if this is really worth it.
- [Crow] I'll distract them
by letting them assault me.
- Look at 'em jump.
Just like rabbits.
- [Tom] Rabbits with
big guns and good aim.
- It ain't supposed
to be this way.
- [Crow] She died as she
lived, failing algebra.
- [Tom] Just tell me
where the mascara is.
Oh jeez.
- Dirty.
- [Mike] Remember guys,
once I carved my name in the
bleachers and there's
a big shootout.
- [Crow] I think we're talking
about full expulsion now.
- Save the rest of your ammo
and lets get out of here.
- [Tom] But we don't
have hall passes!
(gun fires)
- [Mike] Grease, the
version they dared not make.
- Where do we go from here?
- [Crow] Softball practice!
- Sheila's.
She got us into this mess
and she can get us out.
- [Tom] Hey, they're cute.
- From now on we gotta
keep on the move.
- [Mike] She'll do anything
so she doesn't have to drive.
- [Crow] This is
actually a commercial for
Light Days pantie liners.
- [Mike] I wanna buy some.
- [Crow] Officers, close your
eyes so you can't identify us.
Ah forget it they're
too far, quit shooting.
- [Tom] We shot
that fat bar keep.
Thought you were gonna
get the license number.
- [Mike] Well you
said you were gonna
get the license number.
- [Tom] No I didn't ya lobe.
- [Mike] You said it!
- [Tom] No rush just kinda
mosey on into the chase there.
There ya go.
- [Crow] You said you
knew were the chase was.
- [Mike] No you said you knew.
- [Crow] I never.
- [Mike] You said it.
Another right
turn, those fiends!
- [Crow] Tell ya
what, let's not fight,
let's just shoot
any girl we see.
- [Mike] You know the inability
of the cops to turn right
becomes their downfall.
- [Tom] There it is.
- [Crow] The lamp is a
statue of our lady of
do you have a
bathroom around here?
(knock at door)
(doorbell ringing)
- [Crow] Oh right in the
middle of photo play.
- [Mike] She's Judy Jetson.
- Who is it?
- [Paula] Paula.
- What do you want?
- [Paula] Stop talking so
much and open the door.
- [Crow] I barely
said anything god.
- What's up?
- The cops are after us.
- [Tom] Guess which
two of us are dead?
- [Mike] I was just
having a blood communion.
You think my shirt is too baggy?
- How?
- You're in this
as deep as we are.
- Who do you think you're
kidding, get out of here.
- We're staying.
- [Tom] Well,
Crystal Light then.
- What kinda jerks are you
anyway leading the cops
to my door?
- We lost 'em now come
on we want that payoff.
- For what?
- We wrecked the
school like you wanted.
Job completed and job
to be paid for by you.
- [Tom] Well I'll
need an invoice.
- You're out of your minds.
- Are we?
- Well how do I know you
wrecked a school, how?
- Take our word for it
tonight then read about it
in the papers tomorrow.
Oh it'll be in the
papers all right.
Headlines this time.
Now we want our money.
- Yeah, we want
some clothes too.
These things are
a dead giveaway.
- You'll get nothing from me.
- [Crow] I'll go get it.
Hey the famous naked
man, oh what do you know.
- Let's see how long you
stay after I call the cops.
- Keep away from that phone.
I killed a policeman tonight.
- [Mike] Congratulations.
- A cop?
- Yeah, a cop.
- Well I may have
been bluffing before
but I'm not bluffing now.
I'm calling the police.
(gun fires)
- [Crow] Oh and when a woman
that top heavy falls, look out.
Quick Scotch Guard the couch.
- Gotta move fast.
Get a change of clothes.
See what Sheila's got.
- [Mike] That's not
too big in the bust.
- [Crow] Killed
by a tether ball.
- She's awfully young.
- Do ya know her.
- No.
- [Mike] You?
- But I've seen dozens like her.
Lieutenant, there's
another one upstairs.
- [Crow] Well now I've seen
dozens and one I guess.
- [Tom] And after this
let's play some four square.
(equipment whirring)
- Mike, we're ready for you.
- Oh, good.
- The talent will
please find his light.
- Right, uh could we talk
about this 'cause a one man
show about Keanu Reeves,
I don't think that's.
- Darling you are Keanu Reeves.
Pull this off and I'll let
you star in my next epic,
it's a one man show about
Anthony Michael Hall.
- That should be good but
let's talk about the script
for this one I mean--
- Talent to his light please,
final tech rehearsal will
commence places everyone,
oh there you are Margo.
And begin.
- I swear this is the
stupidest thing I've ever done.
This is my own
private Idaho potato.
Oh man that is so lame.
- Lame, it's humor Mike!
- Oh it's stupid, I quit,
Idaho, I quit Crow, I quit.
- Idaho potato it
is funny (laughs).
What, it's a potato.
It's funny!
(funky techno music)
(somber music)
- More cramps?
- Yeah, seems to
be getting worse.
- Maybe something
ya ate at the party.
- Or drank.
- [Crow] So you were in
Austria during the war?
- [Tom] Yeah I was yes.
- [Crow] Hi Mr. Crane.
He's calling the back seat.
You'll never guess
where I'm calling from.
- [Mike] Hey, you seen two
girls in a convertible?
- [Cop] Hey, pull up you two.
- [Crow] Hey that's too far.
Look out, look out,
look out, look out.
Auntie M!
- [Mike] Call glass
replacement specialists
any time day or night.
(ambulance sirens blaring)
- [Mike] Shut it
off, she's gone.
- [Crow] The Simpson's.
- [Tom] The Simpson's.
- [Mike] It's a room in heaven.
- [Crow] Oh mom told me
not to but no I had to
pick that pimple.
- [Mike] You know a federal
indictment may prove
difficult to overcome in
the student elections.
(tense music)
- [Crow] And all
this started because
of their electric kitchen?
- Kids with guns.
- [Mike] Chuck
Heston would love it.
- One of 'em was
killed instantly.
The other one's pretty
badly shaken up.
- [Crow] I'll kill her later.
- Has father been informed?
- Yeah, right
after the accident.
- Oh here he comes now.
- [Crow] Come to see
old slice and dice, eh?
- I wouldn't go
in there just now
if I were you, Carl.
- Paula, she's?
- She's all right.
Can't say the same for
her girlfriend though.
That plate glass window
made quite a mess.
- [Tom] I've got pictures
if you wanna see 'em.
- [Mike] You're lying Phil.
- Have you reached
a verdict yet?
- [Crow] I'm doing it.
- We have your Honor.
- What is that verdict?
- We the jury find
the defendant guilty.
- [Mike] And the opposing jury?
- Will the defendant
please rise.
- [Mike] Look, Emily Bronte.
- [Judge] You have been found
guilty of murder in the first
degree as charged.
- [Crow] You know I
already heard that but it
still upsets me.
- [Mike] She conveys so
much with just a look.
- [Tom] Just that
one single look.
- [Mike] In a related story,
Paula Parkins picked a
pack of pickled peppers.
Sentencing next Tuesday,
appearance by GoGo the gorilla.
- [Narrator] Jam productions.
- [Crow] Hey everybody,
welcome to Tuesday sentencing,
be sure to tip your bailiff.
- [Tom] Here come the me.
- Paula Parkins--
- [Mike] Picked a pack of--
- You have had all that
money can give you,
but that wasn't enough.
You became a thrill seeker.
With an over inflated ego.
This thrill seeking became the
one great thing in your life--
- [Crow] Besides Sun Chips.
- Piling one thrill on
another until with every
increasing intensity you
became much like the drug
addict with his continual--
- [Mike] Drug taking.
- Increases of dosage
until a climax.
A murder.
- [Crow] She almost acted!
- To kill for the
love of killing.
Kill for a thrill.
- [Tom] Kill, kill, kill,
kill, kill, kill, kill.
- Thrill seeker comes
from all walks of life.
The rich as well as the poor.
- [Crow] Hey quit reading
I'm summating here.
- Coming from the home,
a home where the parents
are too busy in their
own affairs to take time
to teach their children
- [Crow] That's us honey.
the importance of
self restraint.
- [Tom] Oh, think he
really captured us.
- So discipline,
politeness, courtesy.
The love for the
mother and the father.
The church.
- [Mike] Your mustache
is falling off sir.
- Their country.
It all adds up to that
one great essential of living.
- [Crow] Ironically this is
still funnier than night court.
- And regard for the property
and feelings of others.
That through this utter
disregard for life itself.
- [Tom] Must stay
awake, must stay awake.
- The thrill seeker
finds his eventual end.
A prisoner of the state.
- [Crow] You're mad aren't you.
- Standing in a court
room convicted of murder
in the first degree.
- [Tom] Look I gotta get
going on my life sentence,
speed it up here.
- Because of your
youth Paula Parkins,
it's impossible for me
to give you the sentence
you so rightfully deserve.
- [Crow] So you get
the spanking machine.
- So I hereby hand it to
the proper institution until
you become 21 years of age.
- [Tom] Then we party, woo.
- [Judge] At which time you
will be transferred to the state
penitentiary for women.
- [Crow] And get a shave
while you're at it.
- Where you will spend the
rest of your natural life.
- [Mike] How's that sound?
(tense music)
Whoa sure screwed up
on that daughter, huh.
- [Tom] Yeah I feel kinda
bad I have to admit.
- [Crow] You know it's actually
a very nice sunny cell.
- [Tom] From one
prison to another.
- [Crow] It's too late to
spend time with her isn't it?
- I don't think I could
drink another cup.
- It passes the time.
- [Mike] You think I
look like Lincoln hunny?
- It's all my fault.
If only I hadn't thought
more of my outside
interests than I did of Paula.
- [Mike] It's okay if I think
it's your fault too isn't it?
- Strong hard lesson
we've been taught.
- [Crow] Live and learn.
- No more your fault
than it is mine.
We're certainly a
fine pair of parents.
- We still have each other.
That's some comfort.
- [Crow] That
supposed to be funny?
- It all seems like
such a bad dream.
- [Mike] Oh like when you're
naked at a hockey game?
- Ever since I
can remember we've
given Paula everything.
Everything but real love.
- [Crow] And peanut butter.
- A new dress
instead of a caress.
A new car instead of--
- [Mike] Instead of a cigar.
- A heart to heart talk.
A new watch.
- [Mike] Instead of a squash.
- It does no good to look back.
Can only be more of a hurt.
We must now look forward.
- [Crow] Let's get a goldfish.
- Using the past only
as a pattern of judgment
for the future.
Paula's lesson to us was strong.
- [Mike] Instead of a thong.
- Her child will
profit by our mistakes.
- [Tom] By the way
ya seen her lately?
I haven't had a
chance to get up there
all the work I got
and everything.
(birds chirping)
- [Crow] Can only stay
for a minute, right?
And what's our excuse?
(funky techno music)
Hi Peggy, Paula,
that's it, Paula.
- How do you feel darling?
- [Mike] Good, real good.
- I don't want my baby
in a place like this.
I don't.
I don't feel so well.
Everything keeps going around.
- We'll see Judge Clara.
We'll take care of everything.
- [Crow] C'mon let's go.
Let's just go, c'mon.
- If only we knew who--
- Everything will be all right.
- [Tom] My rape victim
refuses to come to classes.
- [Mike] Well how's our
little gun-toting trollop?
- That's all now, it's
time you were leaving.
- [Crow] I'm afraid
she's passed away.
- Rest easy now,
it'll be all right.
- We'll see you
when it's all over.
- [Mike] Sometime after
Memorial Day, maybe.
- [Crow] Look I'll send my
secretary to see the baby.
- [Mike] She's got a
room on the 400th floor.
Regrets, I've had a few.
(tragic music)
- So what?
- [Mike] What's your deal,
man, leave us out of it.
- [Crow] Here on
surgery boulevard.
- [Tom] Teeing off at three,
that's all I'm saying.
- [Mike] Maybe I could fund
this as a charity event.
- [Tom] It's your fault.
- [Crow] Now I'm going
to be a bit ugly so you'd
better sit down.
- [Mike] How many arms did she
have when she came in here?
- The baby, a girl,
is well and healthy.
- My daughter, how is she?
- [Crow] I broke her, sorry.
- She, she died.
- [Crow] Well so the life
sentence was really that long.
- [Mike] Not too bad.
- [Crow] Oh easy to do.
- [Mike] Pretty good.
- Some people think newspapers
exaggerate juvenile crime.
- [Crow] We don't can we go.
- Or that it's confined
mostly to large cities.
- [Mike] Dear god.
- This is far from
being the case.
From coast to coast in
small communities as well
as the larger cities.
- [Crow] Even Circle Pines.
- Juvenile delinquency
is on the rise.
- [Mike] I'm playing fast and
loose with my numbers here.
- No child is inherently bad.
- [Tom] Except Paulie Shore.
- He's made what he
is by his upbringing
and his surroundings.
- [Crow] And his
inherently bad parents.
- Thus a parent that
something has gone wrong
with the environment
of a great many
of these children.
Or we wouldn't have this
present delinquency problem.
Adults create the
world children live in
and in this process,
parents play the key role.
When children grow up
among adults who refuse
to recognize anything
that is fine and good
or worthy of respect.
- [Tom] There's a little
joke in Leviticus that says.
- No wonder that many of these
children fail to develop high
moral standards or to
distinguish right from wrong.
- [Mike] Why don't you wrap
it up Judge Pedantic, come on.
- Summed up in
two callous words.
- [Crow] Bor-ing.
- So what?
Juvenile delinquency
is always rooted
in adult delinquency.
- [Tom] Why don't you shut up?
Shut up, shut up,
shut up, shut up, oh!
- Higher moral values can
we hope solve the problem.
- [Mike] Look,
we're double parked.
- The easiest way to bring
this about is through
a return to religion--
- [Mike] Whoa, excuse me,
separation of church and state?
- If all peoples would join
this back to God movement
and bring their
children to respect
the 10 commandments or--
- [Mike] Beat the love
of Jesus into them.
- Other moral laws laid down
by all the great religions.
- [Crow] Your Catholicism,
your polygamy of Thorton eight.
- [Judge] But the time has
come that we must turn our--
- [Crow] Of the
smiles we left behind.
- [Judge] Against the young law
breakers, to protect those--
- [Crow] Hi, again?
- [Judge] Cause mere youth
is no excuse for letting
them remain at large.
Some young criminals are
just as vicious and dangerous
as older criminals.
Law breakers.
- [Crow] But some
crimes are good.
- [Judge] No young
offender should be released
in the custody of his parent,
unless an investigation
shows the parents are--
- [Mike] I can't see this
scene too many times.
- [Judge] If they are not,
a supervision
should be entrusted
to a more responsible agency.
- [Tom] Booze and
jammies don't mix.
- [Judge] And in making
parents financially liable
for property damage
caused by their children
could be especially helpful
against the wave of vandalism
which has been sweeping
across our country.
- [Crow] Even this
adorable vandalism.
- [Judge] With
this responsibility
we're sure that parents
would keep a closer eye
on the kind of fun their
children are having
and that the old
fashion woodshed
would receive more use,
vandalism would decline.
- [Mike] I have no real
proof but it's worth a try,
what the hell?
- [Judge] Some parents
refuse to recognize
the moral obligation--
- [Crow] Count Jugula.
Wow.
- [Judge] When that is the
case, we must take stronger
measures to make them realize
their responsibilities.
- [Crow] Oh my body.
- So you see I cannot
possibly grant the request
for the adoption of this
child of your daughter.
The child must remain a
ward of the state until
such time as a suitable
family can be found.
At that time the child will
be granted to this worthy
family to be brought
up in the world
as it should know the world.
- [Crow] The warm
glow of a state home.
- To you Jane Parkins and
for you Carl Parkins--
- [Tom] Promise to
love, cherish, and obey.
- I can only feel the
deepest of sorrows.
- [Crow] I sentence you to
my toast masters meeting.
- [Tom] Hey, where you two
going, would all the jerkwads
please report to the bathroom?
Thank you.
- [Crow] Tonight on
Hollywood Squares.
Oh wah, I'm an infant,
I'm an infant give
me everything.
(baby crying)
- [Mike] Boy, fun huh?
- [Crow] This was the
feel good movie of 1956.
- [Tom] With a song in
their hearts and a smile
on their faces.
(tense music)
(equipment whirring)
- What are they doing?
- Oh I think they're recreating
the gas station hold
up from the movie.
- Oh.
- Let's watch.
- Wow.
(yawns)
Tom Servo.
Oh, Tom, was it
exciting in the movie?
- Nope.
- Well was it funny?
- Oh.
Well maybe we'd better
read a letter, huh?
- Oh a letter sure!
That's a good idea, there just
happens to be one right here.
- Hey, look at this.
It's an invitation from
a high school graduation
commencement to us.
- Cambot put that
on stilster will ya?
Thanks.
- What's it say there?
Once a driller,
always a driller.
Is that dirty?
- Uh, it depends on
what books you read.
Well it's from Elisa F. Reid
of Bakersfield, California!
- The senior class of
Bakersfield High School
announces its commencement
exercises on Thursday,
the 9th of June 1994 at 7:30
in the evening at
Griffith Field.
Oh that's a nice field.
- Lovely place but I tell ya,
your grandchildren would
be graduating before
we could make it.
So.
- Something's going on.
Woo!
Down to you mad men.
- You see it's a radio
station called Frank.
Rarely is a radio station
named after a person
and when it's give a
solid name like Frank,
well it becomes
campy and endearing.
- Winona.
Vince Gill.
Verlan Husky.
Roger Miller.
- Oh fine don't turn
your cranks to Frank
ya stupid fat heads.
- Tex Raider.
Pat Butram.
Slim Wittman.
Hank Snow.
Marty Robbins.
Nancy Walker.
Sunny Burgess.
Dag Hammershall.
Donna Fargo.
Crispin Glover.
CW McCall.
Zom Fear.
Barbara Mandrell.
Maury Povich.
Coco Chanel.
Earnest Tubb.
Larry Storch.
Jerry Lee Lewis.
Edward Everett Horton.
Gentleman Jim Reeves.
Boss Jim Getties.
Mrs. Miller.
Karen Valentine.
Stonewall Jackson.
Charlie Pride.
- So what.